Guide to the American Planning Association records, 1925-2015.
American Planning Association records,
- APA: Negotiating with Developers - 1 of 3, Undated; V-5645 (Box 85)
- APA: Negotiating with Developers - 2 of 3, Undated; V-5646 (Box 85)
- APA: Negotiating with Developers - 3 of 3, Undated; V-5647 (Box 85)
- Neotraditional Planning: Part of the Planners Toolkit - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5648 (Box 85)
- Neotraditional Planning: Part of the Planners Toolkit - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5649 (Box 85)
- APA: Primer on Constitutional Issues - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5650 (Box 85)
- APA: Primer on Constitutional Issues - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5651 (Box 85)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Primer on Constitutional Issues" - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5652 (Box 85)
- APA: Land Use Law Series - "Primer on Constitutional Issues" - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5653 (Box 85)
- APA: "Shifting Sands" - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5654 (Box 85)
- APA: "Shifting Sands" - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5655 (Box 85)
- AICP Planners Training Service - "Regulations and Affordable Housing", Undated; V-5656 (Box 85)
- Regulations and Affordable Housing, Undated; V-5657 (Box 85)
- Protecting Wildlife In Open Spaces - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5658 (Box 85)
- Protecting Wildlife In Open Spaces - 2 of 2, Undated; V-5659 (Box 85)
- Protecting Wildlife And Open Spaces, Undated; V-5660 (Box 85)
- The Role and Responsibility of the Planning Commissioner - 1 of 2, Undated; V-5661 (Box 85)
- The Role and Responsibility of the Planning Commissioner, Undated; V-5662 (Box 85)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Job of the Commission,", 1997; 0.0716 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Bottom-up Regionalism", 1997; 0.7017 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Grant Writing Skills for Planners", 1997; 0.7018 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Neighborhood Revitatilization and the University", 1997; 0.7019 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"From Auto- to Pedestrian-Oriented Urban Centers", 1997; 0.7020 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Walkable Communities", 1997; 0.7022 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Impact of Takings Legislation", 1997; 0.7024 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Integrating Ecology and Real Estate", 1997; 0.7025 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Fortress America and Gated Communities", 1997; 0.7026 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Strategies for Implementing the Dream", 1997; 0.7027 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Sim City and Beyond", 1997; 0.7028 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Rural Nevada Implements A Master Plan", 1997; 0.7029 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Plannes and Economic Developers", 1997; 0.7030 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"SRO's: More Than Just Housing", 1997; 0.7031 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Neighborhood Planning in the '90s", 1997; 0.7032 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Teaching Sustainability", 1997; 0.7033 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"The Private Sector and Growth Management Initiatives", 1997; 0.7034 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Road Design and Rural Character", 1997; 0.7035 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Habitat Conservation by Essential Service Providers", 1997; 0.7036 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Urban Ballparks", 1997; 0.7037 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Congestion Pricing", 1997; 0.7038 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Small Town Planning in Large Metropolitan Counties", 1997; 0.7039 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Designing Your Own Website", 1997; 0.7040 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"The Lessons Learned in Outlying Communities", 1997; 0.7041 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Community Renewal Through the Arts", 1997; 0.7042 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Calming Takings Disputes", 1997; 0.7043 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Planning Commission as Secret Weapon", 1997; 0.7045 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Where Do We Go From Here?", 1997; 0.7046 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Maintaining Character in Resort Areas", 1997; 0.7047 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"State Planning Laws and the Comprehensive Plan", 1997; 0.7048 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "San Diego/Tijuana Binational Planning", 1997; 0.7049 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Economic Development Conveyances of Bases", 1997; 0.7050 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Multimodal, Multijurisdictional Transportation Planning", 1997; 0.7051 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Community Development Corporations and Economic Development", 1997; 0.7052 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Citizen Diversity and Participation", 1997; 0.7053 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Integrating State Programs", 1997; 0.7054 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"WIS Policies and Practices", 1997; 0.7055 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"New Urbanism on Tobacco Road", 1997; 0.7056 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Housing Today's Families", 1997; 0.7057 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"City Center Plans for Capital Cities", 1997; 0.7058 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Market-Driven Recreational and Entertainment Planning", 1997; 0.7059 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Starting Your Own Consulting Firm", 1997; 0.7060 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"A Coordinated Approach To Code Enforcement", 1997; 0.7061 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Manufactured Housing Institute", 1997; 0.7062 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Environmental Policy for Planners", 1997; 0.7063 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Transfer of Development Credit Programs", 1997; 0.7064 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Neighborhoods and Urban Markets", 1997; 0.7065 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Transportation Planning in World Cities", 1997; 0.7066 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Cutting Edge of CDBG", 1997; 0.7067 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Building Civic Leadership", 1997; 0.7068 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference,"Religions Respond to Preservation", 1997; 0.7069 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Politics and Planners", 1997; 0.7070 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Regulating Dilbert", 1997; 0.7071 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Easing Tourism Tensions", 1997; 0.7072 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Greening Programs For Poor Neighborhoods", 1997; 0.7073 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Comprehensive, Comprehensible Decision Making", 1997; 0.7074 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Adequate Public Facilities for Schools", 1997; 0.7075 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "An Information Superhighway Map", 1997; 0.7076 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Open Space Through Limited Development", 1997; 0.7077 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Anatomy of a Base Reuse", 1997; 0.7078 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Market-Based Comprehensive Planning", 1997; 0.7079 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Community Indicators", 1997; 0.7080 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Linear Corridor Planning", 1997; 0.7081 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Rural Home-Based Businesses", 1997; 0.7082 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "New Opportunities for Low-Income Families", 1997; 0.7083 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Economic and Aesthetic Impacts of Signs", 1997; 0.7084 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Telecommunications Reform Act of 1996 and FCC Preemption Rules", 1997; 0.7085 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning for the Mornings After", 1997; 0.7086 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Brave New World of Telecommunications", 1997; 0.7087 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, New Planners in the Job Market", 1997; 0.7088 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "New Directions in Sustainable Development", 1997; 0.7089 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Land Use and Environmental Case Law", 1997; 0.7090 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Partnerships for Low-Income Minority Housing", 1997; 0.7091 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Countryside Stewardship Exchange", 1997; 0.7092 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "GIS In Right-of-Way Planning", 1997; 0.7093 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning Support Systems", 1997; 0.7094 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Women Planners in Transition", 1997; 0.7095 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Small Town, Big Opportunities", 1997; 0.7096 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Strategic Planning for Communities", 1997; 0.7097 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Cost of Urban Sprawl", 1997; 0.7098 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Ending Homelessness", 1997; 0.7099 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Community Involvement in Transit Planning", 1997; 0.7100 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "From Traffic Calming to Circulation Planning", 1997; 0.7101 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Sweet Istea?", 1997; 0.7102 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "True Costs of Growth Management", 1997; 0.7103 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Continuing Professional and Citizen Education", 1997; 0.7104 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "I Don't Get No Respect", 1997; 0.7105 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "High-Tech, High-Access Code System", 1997; 0.7106 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Tribal Planning on Reservations", 1997; 0.7107 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Planner's Role in Natural Hazard Mitigation", 1997; 0.7108 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Mega Events and Community Development", 1997; 0.7109 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "AICP Exam Prep Session I", 1997; 0.7110 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Istrea Reauthorization Workshop", 1997; 0.7111 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Professional Development and Career Opportunities", 1997; 0.7112 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Accessible Sidewalks", 1997; 0.7113 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Fiscal Stress in Small Towns", 1997; 0.7114 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Reinventing Affordable Housing", 1997; 0.7115 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning After Ehrlich", 1997; 0.7116 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Report From Habitat II", 1997; 0.7117 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "International Planning Exchange", 1997; 0.7118 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "From Graphite to Gigabyte", 1997; 0.7119 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning the Capital", 1997; 0.7120 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning Law for Planning Commissioners", 1997; 0.7121 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Addressing Regional Issues in the Devolution Revolution", 1997; 0.7122 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Area-Based Planning", 1997; 0.7123 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Data Sharing Between Agencies", 1997; 0.7124 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Gaining Strength Through Planning", 1997; 0.7125 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Changing Planning Departments", 1997; 0.7126 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Mega Planning for Mega Events", 1997; 0.7127 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Zoning the Big Box", 1997; 0.7128 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "HUD Consolidated Planning Software Workshop", 1997; 0.7129 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, Rebuilding Neighborhood Business Districts", 1997; 0.7130 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Technology and Communities in Transition", 1997; 0.7131 (Box 81)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Economic Development Innovations", 1993; 311 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Neotraditionalism in the Real World", 1993; 312 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Affordable housing and Regulatory Barriers", 1993; 313 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Urban Design as a Planning Element", 1993; 314 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The State Role in Planning and Growth Management", 1993; 315 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Total Quality Management", 1993; 316 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "America's Cities, What Works", 1993; 317 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning Ethics and Practice", 1993; 318 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Keynote Session Featuring Maynard Jackson", 1993; 319 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Growth Management Lessons for the Heartland", 1993; 320 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Computer-Adided Visualization", 1993; 321 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Better Decision-Making for Planning Commissioners", 1993; 322 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Urban Policy Challenges for Planning", 1993; 323 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Management by Feedback", 1993; 324 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Community as a Resource for Education", 1993; 325 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Intermodal Transportation", 1993; 326 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Encouraging Affordable Housing", 1993; 327 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning, Research, and Tourism Partnerships", 1993; 328 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Water Quality 2000", 1993; 329 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Working Together: Roles of the Design Professionals", 1993; 330 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Universities Roles in Community Planning", 1993; 331 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Challenge of Rural Diversity", 1993; 332 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The 1893 Fair and the 1909 Plan of Chicago", 1993; 333 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Protection of Freshwater Wetlands", 1993; 334 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Empowering Children", 1993; 335 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Barcelona, Atlanta, and the Olympics", 1993; 336 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Transportation Planning Under Istea", 1993; 337 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Community Credit Needs Assessment", 1993; 339 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Forum on the Agenda for America's Communities", 1993; 340 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Land-Use Law for Planning Commissioners", 1993; 341 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Large-Scale Urban Models", 1993; 357 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Back to Basics in Houston", 1993; 358 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Reinventing Government", 1993; 359 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "How to Deal with Difficult People", 1993; 361 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Resorts and Tourism Forum", 1993; 362 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning and Federal Agencies", 1993; 363 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "First Amendment Issues in Planning Law", 1993; 364 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Improving Relations Between Commission and Staff", 1993; 365 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Desktop Software for Planners I", 1993; 366 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Future of Electric Power I", 1993; 367 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning after Disasters", 1993; 368 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Future of Electric Power II", 1993; 369 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "So You've Been Sued?", 1993; 370 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning for Ecological Restoration", 1993; 371 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Military Closings", 1993; 372 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning in Latin America", 1993; 373 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Developer's Point of View", 1993; 374 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Desktop Software for Planners II", 1993; 375 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The Americans with Disabilities Act", 1993; 376 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Achieving adn Preserving Racial Diversity", 1993; 377 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "AICP Exam Review Course II", 1993; 378 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Diversity in the Workplace", 1993; 380 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning and Sharing Power", 1993; 381 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Reverse Commuting", 1993; 382 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Contract Management", 1993; 383 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Lobbying Skills for Planners", 1993; 384 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Development Agreements and Annexation Agreements", 1993; 385 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Community and the New Urban Village", 1993; 386 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Green Cities", 1993; 397 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planning Commission Training Programs", 1993; 398 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Sustainability and Community Renewal", 1993; 399 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Principles and Practice of Design Review", 1993; 3101 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Maintaining Small Town Character", 1993; 3102 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Managing Growth and Performance Standards", 1993; 3103 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "The 1893 World's Columbian Exposition", 1993; 3104 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Transportation and Neighborhood Revitalization", 1993; 3105 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Greenways for Chicago", 1993; 3106 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Urban Media Forum", 1993; 3108 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Planners Facing Unemployment", 1993; 3109 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Black Women Planners Professional Network", 1993; 3110 (Box 82)
- APA National Planning Conference, "AICP Planners Workshop: The Planner's Role in Capital Improvements", 1992; 295 (Box 83)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Successful Citizen Surveys", 1992; 296 (Box 83)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Evaluating Planning Agencies", 1992; 297 (Box 83)
- APA National Planning Conference, "Zoning in Central Cities", 1992; 298 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "Using Video and Cable TV", 299 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "Hot Topoics in Resort Communities", 2100 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "AICP Workshop: Practical Solutions to Management Problems", 2101 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "A New National Program: Scenic Byways", 2102 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "The 1990 Affordable Housing Act", 2103 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "AICP Exam Review Course II", 2104 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "Grassroots Planning and Design", 2121 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "The Blackstone River Valley Heritage Corner", 2123 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "The Transportation and Land Use Connection", 2124 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "Counties and Cities: Trust and Distrust", 2125 (Box 83)
- APA 1992 APA National Planning Conference, "Helping Minority Communities Plan", 2126 (Box 83)
- APA: Livable Communities and Sustainable Development, Undated; V-5667 (Box 84)
- APA: The Best of Planning for Zoning Administrators, 1994; V-5668 (Box 84)
- APA: Using Scientific Information for Better Planning, 2001; V-5669 (Box 84)
- APA: Training Made Easy, Undated; V-5670 (Box 84)
- APA: Lincoln Institute of Land Policy - Transfer of Development Rights Revisted, 2000; V-5671 (Box 84)
- APA: Infill Development and the Redesign of Suburban Centers, Undated; V-5672 (Box 84)
- Electronic Town Meeting: Planning for the Information Age, Undated; V-5673 (Box 84)
- APA: Washington Hilton and The Omni Shoreham Hotel Celebrate Community - Washington, DC, 2004; V-5674 (Box 84)
- APA: Washington Hilton and The Omni Shoreham Hotel Celebrate Community - Washington, DC, 2004 (Box 137 and 138)
- APA: 2005 National Planning Conference - San Francisco, CA, V-5675 (Box 84)
- APA: The Best of Community Planning CD-ROM, V-5676 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 1 of 7, 2004; CD-989 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 2 of 7, 2004; CD-990 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 3 of 7, 2004; CD-991 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 4 of 7, 2004; CD-992 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 5 of 7, 2004; CD-993 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 6 of 7, 2004; CD-994 (Box 84)
- APA: National Planning Conference, Washington, DC CD-ROM - 7 of 7, 2004; CD-995 (Box 84)
- AICP: Managers Planning Guide to Improving the Development Review System CD-ROM, Undated; CD-996 (Box 84)
- AICP Examination Preparation Course CD-ROM #1, Undated; CD-997 (Box 84)
- AICP Examination Preparation Course CD-ROM #2, Undated; CD-998 (Box 84)
- AICP Examination Preparation Course CD-ROM #3, Undated; CD-999 (Box 84)
- Datachem Software: LanPlanPrep Version 1.0 CD-ROM, Undated; CD-1000 (Box 84)
- APA: The Best of Contemporary Community Planning CD-ROM, 2002; CD-1001 (Box 84)
- APA: Design Review - From Historic Preservation to Site Plans, Undated; V-5663 (Box 86)
- APA: Historic Preservation and Downtown Renewal, Undated; V-5664 (Box 86)
- APA: Electronic Town Meetings, Undated; V-5665 (Box 86)
- APA: The Legal Foundation for Planning Commission and Zoning Board Decisions, Undated; V-5666 (Box 86)
- APA: Developing and Streamlining Zoning Administration, Undated; V-5667 (Box 86)
- National APA Conference, "Regulating Incompatible Land Uses", 1987; 732 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning, Women, and Politics", 1987; 734 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Real Estate Development and Public Works", 1987; 735 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning the World's Major Metropolis", 1987; 736 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Plenary Luncheon", 1987; 737 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Impact Fee Administration", 1987; 738 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Growth Management Goes Downtown", 1987; 739 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Low-Income Cooperatives: Innovative Approaches", 1987; 740 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Quasi-Public Institutional Participation in Planning", 1987; 741 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Unpredictable Regulation", 1987; 742 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Wall Street to Main Street: Financing Your America", 1987; 743 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Planning for Child Care: Public-Sector Success Stories", 1987; 744 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Urban Entrepreneurship", 1987; 745 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Winning the Media Campaign", 1987; 746 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Transitional Housing", 1987; 747 (Box 87)
- National APA Conference, "Transportation and Economic Development: the Application of Impact Fees", 1987; 748 (Box 87)